<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on XLing Labs | UMass</title>
    <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on XLing Labs | UMass</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://xlingumass.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes on IRB</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/irb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/irb/</guid>
      <description>Plan well, plan ahead! Your protocol must be submitted, reviewed and approved in writing by the IRB via UMass e-Protocol before you can start a study. IRB approval can take 4-6 weeks and is valid for a maximum period of one year (unless the study was found to be exempt, in which case it’s three years).
Important deadlines Applications not requiring full board review are reviewed on a rolling basis upon submission of all necessary materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RA Guide</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/ra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/ra/</guid>
      <description>RA Guide Human Subjects training CITI training RAs must complete this online training in order to run human subjects at UMass. Take the Group 2 course; it generally takes about 1-2 hours to finish, though you have the option to save your progress and return to it later. RAs should forward the link to their certificate of completion to the lab manager.
Psychological and Brain Sciences ethics training Attending PBS ethics training is mandatory for any undergraduates using the Psych pool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding and Editing Posts</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, welcome to the new XLing Labs site. This should be a flexible new framework for the lab and its members to highlight new work and documentation. It&amp;rsquo;s also a good place to put common information like scheduling!
In this document I&amp;rsquo;m going to break down some of the basic actions you can do to expand this website. We&amp;rsquo;re going to cover, first, how you can edit an existing page on the website and later, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss how you can add whole new pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eyetracking Guides</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/eyetracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/eyetracking/</guid>
      <description>Single line reading experiments Gathering data Creating a region file for your items Create a text file of your stimuli, then insert region boundaries using forward slashes. This needs to be done for every line; consider using greps to do this automatically (see here).
!!! tip &amp;ldquo;Regioning conventions&amp;rdquo; - For a given critical word or words, the whitespace before it is typically included in the region. - There MUST be a backslash on the final region, before the newline &amp;lsquo;\n&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ibex Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/ibex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/ibex/</guid>
      <description>The Ibex Farm is a hosted version of the Ibex software, created by Alex Drummond. We do not currently host our own version of the software.
Before running an Ibex experiment, check:
  Do you have proper IRB approval?
  Do you have up-to-date CITI training?
  First things first: documentation To learn to run an Ibex experiment, check out the following resources:
 The Ibex manual. This is the authoritative manual on Ibex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSF</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/osf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/osf/</guid>
      <description>Open Science Federation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phonetics Guides</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/phonetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/phonetics/</guid>
      <description>Phoneme Categorization In a phoneme categorization experiment, a listener is presented with a single stimulus on each trial, and they have to assign that stimulus to one or another category. It&amp;rsquo;s possible that the listener may be given more than just two categories to choose from but that&amp;rsquo;s rare in the experiments run in our lab.
Usually, each stimulus is one of a sequence of stimuli that steps incrementally from a good instance of one category to a good instance of another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sona</title>
      <link>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/sona/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xlingumass.github.io/docs/sona/</guid>
      <description>We schedule sessions and recruit participants via the Linguistics SONA. Participating members of the Linguistics faculty have either given us the rosters of their classes, or given their students the option to create a SONA account and participate in experiments for extra credit or as part of an assignment. Only students may request accounts &amp;ndash; to get an account as a researcher or instructor, email the lab manager.
For help using SONA, refer to the manual .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
